Mss.Ms.Coll.115
American Philosophical Society
- Series IX. Kane Family Miscellany, 1793-1973; Architectural drawings, photographs, newspaper clippings, family biographies, pamphlets, address books, and notebooks from 1793-1973.
  - Eliza Middleton Kane Cope, 1884-1973
    - Photographs--oversize, Undated
      Black and white photographs of Cope children and grandchildren.
    - Poems, prayers, Undated
- Series X. Bound Volumes, 1816-1875; Account, receipt and roll books, diaries, letterbooks, and legal notes from 1816-1875.
  - John Kintzing Kane, 1816-1861
    - Account with the Commercial Bank of Pennsylvania, 1830-1836; No. 1; 1.0 vol.
    - Account with the Farmers and Merchants Bank, 1838-1847; No. 2; 1.0 vol.
    - Check book, 1849-1853; No. 3a; 1.0 vol.
    - Check book, 1853-1854; No. 3b; 1.0 vol.
    - Receipt book, 1824-1836; No. 4a; 1.0 vol.
    - Receipt book, 1844-1858; No. 4b; 1.0 vol.
    - Receipt book, 1851-1857; No. 4c; 1.0 vol.
    - Account book, 1818-1822; No. 5a; 1.0 vol.
    - Account book, 1858-1861; No. 5b; 1.0 vol.
    - Estate account book, 1858; No. 6; 1.0 vol.
    - Memoranda respecting professional business for Girard Bank, etc., 1840-1841; No. 7; 1.0 vol.
    - Roll book, 1856; No. 8; 1.0 vol.
      Contains two sketches of ship captains.
    - Legal book, 1856; No. 9; 1.0 vol.
    - Legal notes, 1816; No. 10; 1.0 vol.
    - Trial list, United States Circuit Court, Eastern District of Pennsylvania, 1847; No. 11; 1.0 vol.
      With many newspaper clippings on court decisions.
    - Commonplace book, 1817; No. 12a; 1.0 vol.
    - Commonplace book, 1817-1818; No. 12b; 1.0 vol.
    - Commonplace book, 1818; No. 12c; 1.0 vol.
    - Farmers and Mechanics Bank book, Undated; No. 13; 1.0 vol.
    - Estate. Farmers and Mechanics Bank book., Undated; No. 14; 1.0 vol.
    - Checkbook on the Farmers and Mechanics Bank, 1857; No. 15; 1.0 vol.
    - Letter copy book, 1816-1820
  - Robert Patterson Kane, 1838-1872
    - Diary, 1858; No. 1; 1.0 vol.
    - Letterbook, 1853-1858; No. 2a; 1.0 vol.
    - Letterbook, 1864-1872; No. 2b; 1.0 vol.
    - Notebook of legal cases, Undated; No. 3a; 1.0 vol.
    - Notebook of legal cases, Undated; No. 3b; 1.0 vol.
    - Young Men's Breckenridge, Lane and Foster Club of Philadelphia, 1860; No. 4
    - Notebook of office affairs, 1858; No. 5; 1.0 vol.
    - Docket book, Undated; No. 6; 1.0 vol.
    - Mathematical notebook, 1838; No. 8; 1.0 vol.
    - Account with the Pennsylvania Company..., Undated; No. 9; 1.0 vol.
  - Eliza Middleton Kane Cope, 1875
    - Herbarium book, 1875
      Album of pressed flowers from Italy.